# **HASHMATULLAH AFROZ**

Crawley, Gatwick London, Southgate Avenue +447424132003 | zaherhashmatullah1@gmail.com

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am an experienced software developer. I bring more than four years experience writing PHP full-stack applications, javascript, Django and more than three years experience in the technology industry. Duo to my qualification, extensive background, training, I am interested to apply for the vacant position and join your respected team. That will be really kind of you if you do a closer look at the particulars of my education and skills which you find on my CV. I am very confident of Management, Supervision, Monitoring, evaluation, Coordinating, reporting, Analysing, interpreting, team work, have good speaking voice, neat and respectable appearance, Ability and willingness of working outside normal office hours

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### AWCC

2018 - 2020

Customer care

Greeting the customers offer them credit cards and also i was saling the cards in one side

## British Council

2016 - 2017

Invigilator

Control and organize candidates during exam day

## Azerakhsh Academic Centre

2016 - 2016

Teacher

# Diamond Gym

2021 - 2022

Freelancer

I developed a CMS for the gym, it was a localhost database and i was maintain the database to them

## AM&M (Accelerated Mail& Marketing)

2022 - Upto Now

Full stack Web Developer

lam a full stack web developer in the company i am developing website for the clients and making secure and updating the websites that already have developed, lam administrating the databases and also lam doing some IT works like upgrading windows, configuration of new PC with the network iam also working with active directories.

## **EDUCATION**

# Bakhtar Unversity

2018-2022

Computer Science, Software Engineering

## Habibya High School

2017

89.89%

#### Azerakhsh Academic Centre

2015 - 2016

English literature

# **SKILLS**

- Basics of C/C++ programming language
- C# Programming language game development (Unity)
- Basics of Java Programming Language
- JavaScript (Full-Stack Developer)
- Basics of Python Programming Language
- FRONT-END Web development HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, React.JS
- BACK-END(Server) Development: Laravel(PHP), PHP PDO, Express.JS (Node.js), MVC pattern, Basics of Django (python) MVT pattern
- DATABASE Development : MySQL(RDBMS), MangoDB(non-relational), SQLlite3(RDBMS)
- Mobile Development : React-Native(JavaScript) IOS and Android
- Networking and reconnaissance (PT) Familiar with Linux OS

## **PROJECTS**

# Gym Management

Manipulating data, creating reports, Authorization, authentication and so on

#### Restaurant

Creating reports, Analysing Data, manipulating data and so on

# My portfolio

You can check my portfolio here. https://hashmatullahafroz.github.io/Hashmatullah-Afroz-portfolio

# Github

https://github.com/HashmatullahAfroz

## My LinkedIn

You can check my skills in my LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/hashmatullah-afroz-0a53a0249

# **LANGUAGES**

- Dari
- Pashto
- English
- Urdu
- Arabic

# **REFERENCE**

Bezhan Rasuly - "AWCC"

Team Leader +93700801773